A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accession 2017:050 FA1304
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Publications, 1
  - Just Growth: Inclusion and Prosperity in America's Metropolitan Regions, Regional Studies Association, Regions and Cities, Chris Benner and Manuel Pastor, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 848)
  - Equity, Growth, and Community: What the Nation Can Learn from America's Metro Areas, Chris Benner and Manuel Pastor, 2015 (Box 64, Folder 849)
  - Confronting Suburban Poverty in America, Elizabeth Kneebone and Alan Berube, 2013 (Box 64, Folder 850)
  - Government & Philanthropic Innovations in Place-Based Approaches: Southeast Kentucky, Fresno, California, Pine Ridge, South Dakota, undated (Box 64, Folder 851)
  - About Community, Not a Commute: Investing Beyond the Rail, 2016 (Box 64, Folder 852)
  - Policy for Local Progress: Case Studies & Best Practices From Around the Country, Local Progress: The National Municipal Policy Network, undated (Box 64, Folder 853)
  - All-In Nation: An American that Works for All, A Collaboration Between the Center for American Progress and PolicyLink, Vanessa Cardenas and Sarah Treuhaft, undated (Box 65, Folder 854)
  - Rewriting the Rules of the American Economy: An Agenda for Growth and Shared Prosperity, Joseph E. Stiglitz, Roosevelt Institute, 2015 (Box 65, Folder 855)
  - All On Board: Making Inclusive Growth Happen, Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) and Ford Foundation, undated (Box 65, Folder 856)
  - Topographical Policy Assessment: The Economic Opportunity Policy Landscape in Minnesota, 2012 August 28 (Box 65, Folder 857)
  - Transition and Tension in Southeast Asia: An Experimental Series of Programs for Group Discussion - Part I, Nathaniel Peffer, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 858)
  - Transition and Tension in Southeast Asia: An Experimental Series of Programs for Group Discussion - Part II, Nathaniel Peffer, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 859)
  - Exploring the Ways of Mankind, Walter Goldschmidt, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 860)
  - Exploring the Ways of Mankind: Special Edition for Adult Study Groups, Walter Goldschmidt, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 861)
  - Readings in the Ways of Mankind 1, Walter Goldschmidt, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 862)
  - Readings in the Ways of Mankind 2, Walter Goldschmidt, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 863)
  - Fund for Adult Education - Humanities Paperback Textbooks (5 books), 1953-1958 (Box 66, Folder 864)
  - Discussion Leader's Guide for Use with Discovering Modern Poetry, Elizabeth Drew and George Connor, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 865)
  - An Introduction to The Humanities: Book of Readings and Music Supplement, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 866)
  - The Jeffersonian Heritage, Dumas Malone, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 867)
  - Jefferson and Our Times: A Series of Study-Discussion Programs Prepared By Dumas Malone, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 868)
  - Discovering Modern Poetry, Elizabeth Drew and George Connor, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 869)
  - An Introduction to the Humanities: A Study-Discussion Program for Adults, Humanities Staff of the College of the University of Chicago, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 870)
  - An Introduction to the Humanities, Participant's Manual, Including a Guide for Discussion Leaders, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 871)
  - Education for a Free Society: Selected Papers on Political and Personal Freedom, the Content of Liberal Learning and the Role of the Teacher in America, Alexander Meiklejohn, The Fund for Adult Education, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 872)
  - Education for a Free Society - Part II: Selected Papers on Political and Personal Freedom, the Content of Liberal Learning and the Role of the Teacher in America, Alexander Meiklejohn, The Fund for Adult Education, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 873)
  - Discovering Modern Poetry: A Series of Study and Discussion Programs for Adult Groups, undated (Box 68, Folder 874)
  - The Shape of Our Cities: A Series of Study-Discussion Programs on Urbanism Prepared by Dean Jose Luis Sert & Jacqueline Tyrwhitt, Graduate School of Design, Harvard University, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 875)
  - Job #96-05A: 1995 President's Review - General, 1995-1997 (Box 68, Folder 876)
  - Job #96-05B: 1995 President's Review - Lists Done, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 877)
  - Job #96-12B: A World in Need of Leadership: Tomorrow's U.N. - A Fresh Appraisal - Lists, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 878)
  - Job #96-12C: A World in Need of Leadership: Tomorrow's U.N. - A Fresh Appraisal: Who Speaks for the Hungry?, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 879)
  - Job #96-14A: Innovations in American Government - 10th Anniversary - General, 1996-1998 (Box 69, Folder 880-881)
  - Job #96-15: African Studies in the United States: A Perspective, 1996-1998 (Box 69, Folder 882)
  - Job #96-17A: 1996 Annual Report - General, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 883)
  - Job #96-17C: 1996 Annual Report - Officers/Trustees, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 884)
  - Job #96-17D: 1996 Annual Report - Letters to Congress, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 885)
  - Job #96-17E: 1996 Annual Report - Representatives, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 886)
  - Job #96-17F: 1996 Annual Report - Offprint, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 887)
    Includes Statement of Investments 1996
  - Job #96-17G: 1996 Annual Report - Poll Card, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 888-889)
  - 1996 Ford Foundation Annual Report (2 copies), 1997 March (Box 70, Folder 890)
  - The Educational Endowment Series - The Law and the Lore of Endowment Funds: Report to the Ford Foundation, William L. Cary and Craig B. Bright, 1969 April (Box 70, Folder 891)
  - The School and The Democratic Environment: Papers and Other Materials Drawn From a Conference Sponsored by the Danforth Foundation and the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1970 (Box 71, Folder 892)
  - Social Science Research on Business: Product and Potential, Robert A. Dahl, Mason Haire, and Paul F. Lazarsfeld, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 893)
  - Toward Humanistic Education: A Curriculum of Affect, Edited by Gerald Weinstein & Mario D. Fantini (4 copies, paperback and hardcover versions), 1970 (Box 71, Folder 894, Box 111, Folder 1297)
  - Minority Access to College: A Ford Foundation Report, Fred E. Crossland (2 copies), 1971 (Box 71, Folder 895)
  - Ford Foundation Travel and Study Grants, 1964-1968 (2 copies), 1969 July (Box 72, Folder 896)
  - Report of the Study for the Ford Foundation on Policy and Program (2 copies), 1949 November (Box 72, Folder 897)
  - Forestry for Sustainable Rural Development: A Review of Ford Foundation-Supported Community Forestry Programs in Asia, 1998 March (Box 72, Folder 898)
  - Current Interests of the Ford Foundation, 1994 and 1995 (3 copies), 1994 September (Box 72, Folder 899)
  - Backs Against the Wall: Urban-Oriented Colleges and Universities and the Urban Poor and Disadvantaged, Pastora San Juan Cafferty and Gail Spangenberg (2 copies), 1983 (Box 72, Folder 900, Box 112, Folder 1307)
  - The Gender and Reproductive Health Impacts of Health Sector Reform in Asia, Kunming Medical College, Ford Foundation, Lijiang, Yunnan Province, China, 2000 March 12-17 (Box 72, Folder 901)
  - Indigenous Ways of Knowing, Presented to the Ford Foundation, 2007 January 16 (Box 72, Folder 902)
    An Exploration in Diversity and Curriculum Development: The Indigenous Ways of Knowing Project at Lewis and Clark College
  - Peace and Social Justice - Ford Foundation (2 copies), 2003 (Box 72, Folder 903, Box 110, Folder 1293)
    Building a more secure and equitable world through governance, civil society, and human rights; Folder also includes Publications from the Ford Foundation (1973)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government, 1994: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1994 September (Box 73, Folder 904)
  - Bulletin: The Ford Foundation, New Delhi Office, Winter 1998 - Preserving India's Cultural Heritage (Box 73, Folder 905)
  - Bulletin: The Ford Foundation, New Delhi Office, Spring/Summer 1999 - Putting the Last First (Box 73, Folder 906)
  - The Urgency of Now - Ford Foundation 2007 Annual Report (Box 73, Folder 907)
  - 2nd Learning Workshop on Representing Class, Ethnicity, Gender, and Race to the Public, Irma McClaurin, 2007 February 1-2 (Box 73, Folder 908)
  - Report on the 2nd Learning Workshop on Representing Class, Ethnicity, Gender, and Race to the Public, Irma McClaurin, 2007 February 1-2 (Box 73, Folder 909)
  - The National Women's Studies Association (NWSA): A Report for the Ford Foundation, Gina Ulysse, 2005 November 30 (Box 73, Folder 910)
  - Women's Studies Centers: A Report to the Ford Foundation, Gina Ulysse, 2006 January 21 (Box 73, Folder 911)
  - Unfinished Business: Black Women's Studies, 1995-2005: A Ford Foundation Internal Report Prepared by Dr. Gina Ulysse, Consultant, 2005 December 9 (Box 73, Folder 912)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Media Coverage, 1992 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 913-914)
    Sections include: National Media, Trades, Local Media, Los Angeles, CA (Humanitas), Los Angeles (ASTAC), Kansas (Environmental Clean Up), Cambridge, MA (City Works), Quincy, MA (Court Domestic Abuse Program), New York State (Child Assistance Program), New York City (Fleet Improvement Program), Arlington, VA (Bilingual Outreach), Washington State (Workers Compensation Project), Spokane, WA (Elderly Services), Finalists/Other Coverage
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Media Coverage (2 copies), 1993 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 915-916, Box 113, Folder 1311-1312)
    Sections include: National Media/Wires, Advertisements, Trades, Columns, Editorials, Winners, California (Info/California), Los Angeles (Telecommuting Program), Michigan (Computer Learning Ctrs.), New York (CPESS), Ohio (GAUL), Oregon (Vendo Information Program), South Carolina (Police Homeowners Loan Program), Texas (Child Care Mgmt Services), Washington (Community Voice Mail), West Virginia (LAMP), Finalists, Semifinalists/Other Coverage
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Media Coverage (Box 74, Folder 917-918)
    Sections include: National Media, Advertisements, Trades, Columns, Editorials, Winners, Arizona (Quickcourt), California (Coles Levee Ecosystem Preserve), Massachusetts (Score), Minnesota Voluntary Investigation and Cleanup, Minnesota (Parents' Fair Share), New Hampshire (Here, Thayer, and Everywhere), New York (Partnerships for Long-Term Care), New York (Citywide Central Insurance Program), Oklahoma (SANE), Oregon (Benchmarks), Finalists, Semifinalists, 1993 Winners, Other
  - Innovations in American Government 1995 - News Clips (Box 74, Folder 919-920)
    Sections include: National Media, Advertisements, Trades, Winners, Finalists, Semifinalists, Previous Winners, Video News Release
  - Innovations in State and Local Government - Press Clippings - An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation and the John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 921)
    Sections include: National Coverage, Alaska, Local Coverage, Florida, Iowa, Maryland, Massachusetts, Minnesota, New York, Virginia, Washington, Other Finalists
  - Innovations in State and Local Government - Press Clippings - An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation and the John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University (2 copies), 1991 (Box 75, Folder 922-923, Box 113, Folder 1310)
    Sections include: National Coverage, Local Coverage, California (San Diego County), Georgia, Kentucky, Maryland, Massachusetts, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Tennessee, Washington, Other Finalists
  - The 1988 Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program - Public Relations Activity Report, Public Interest Public Relations (PIPR), 1988 November (Box 75, Folder 924)
  - From Gatekeeper to Gateway: Transforming Testing in America, Report of the National Commission on Testing and Public Policy - Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 925)
    Sections include: News Stories and Editorials
  - Leadership Program for Community Foundations, Round III, The Ford Foundation and the John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 926)
    Sections include: General, Leadership Grants, Delaware Community Foundation, Duluth-Superior Area Community Foundation, Fargo-Moorhead Area Foundation, The Foundation of Greater Greensboro, Maine Community Foundation, The Rockland Community Trust, Sacramento Regional Foundation, Greater Santa Cruz County Community Foundation, The Vermont Community Foundation
  - A World in Need of Leadership: Tomorrow's United Nations, A Study Made Possible by the Ford Foundation and the Dag Hamarskjöld Foundation - Press Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 927)
    Sections include: National Coverage, International Coverage, and Letters
  - National Academic Achievement and Transfer Project, Public Response to a New Initiative of The American Council on Education and the Ford Foundation - Press Clippings, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 928)
    Sections include: Editorial Comment, News Stories, and Associated Press
  - Ford Foundation Program-Related Investments (PRI), 1983 March (Box 75, Folder 929)
  - Reflections & Resonance: Stories of Chinese Women Involved in International Preparatory Activities for the 1995 NGO Forum on Women (2 copies), 1995 March (Box 75, Folder 930, Box 111, Folder 1296)
  - Competition in the U.S. Energy Industry: A Report to the Energy Policy Project of the Ford Foundation, Thomas D. Duchesneau, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 931)
  - Selected Studies on Energy, Background Papers for Energy: The Next Twenty Years, Hans H. Landsberg, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 932)
  - Energy and U.S. Foreign Policy, A Report to the Energy Policy Project of the Ford Foundation, Joseph A. Yager and Eleanor B. Steinberg of the Brookings Institution, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 933)
  - Perspective on Power, A Report to the Energy Policy Project of the Ford Foundation, Edward Berlin, Charles J. Cicchetti, and William J. Gillen, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 934)
  - Welfare: The Elusive Consensus: Where We Are, How We Got There, and What's Ahead, A Report from the Welfare Policy Project of the Ford Foundation and Duke University, Lester M. Salamon (2 copies), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 935)
    With an essay on the Carter Welfare Program by Harvey D. Shapiro
  - Education and Development Reconsidered: The Bellagio Conference Papers, Ford Foundation/Rockefeller Foundation, F. Champion Ward (2 copies), 1974 (Box 77, Folder 936-937)
  - The Ford Foundation's Neighborhood and Family Initiative, The Challenge of Sustainability: An Interim Report, Robert J. Chaskin, Selma Chipenda Dansokho, and Mark L. Joseph (2 copies), 1997 July (Box 78, Folder 938)
    Covering the period January 1995-October 1996, The Neighborhood and Family Initiative Evaluation Project, The Chapin Hall Center for Children, University of Chicago
  - A Ford Foundation Report: The New Delhi Seminar on Media, Government, and the Law, Ann Lapping (4 copies - green and fuchsia covers), 1980 December (Box 78, Folder 939, Box 112, Folder 1309)
    Seminar took place August 24-27, 1978, New Delhi
  - Latino Research Center Development Program: A Preliminary Report, Inter-University Program for Latino Research, Maria Chacón, 1992 February (Box 78, Folder 940)
  - Job 90-15: Ford Foundation & China (Revised Version), 1991 (Box 78, Folder 941)
  - Job 90-16: Ford Foundation in the Soviet Union & Eastern Europe (Russian Version), 1990-1992 (Box 78, Folder 942)
  - Job 90-21: El Bien Comun (Common Good), 1991-1994 (Box 78, Folder 943)
  - Job 90-21: Lists for El Bien Comun, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 944)
  - Job 90-28: Recovering our Confidence: New York and the Civic Spirit, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 945)
  - Job 93-17A: Renewing the UN System - General Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 79, Folder 946-948)
  - Job 93-17C: Renewing the UN System - Letterhead, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 949)
  - Job 93-17D: Renewing the UN System - Press Materials, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 950)
  - Job 93-17E: Renewing the UN System - Lists, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 951-952)
  - Job 93-17F: Renewing the UN System - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 953)
  - Ford Foundation Current Interests 2005 (Box 80, Folder 954)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation Eastern Africa (3 copies, 2 editions), 2006 (Box 80, Folder 955)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation Southern Africa (2 copies), 2014 (Box 80, Folder 956)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation Mexico and Central America (2 English copies, 2 Spanish copies), 2011 (Box 80, Folder 957)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation Vietnam (2 English copies, 2 Vietnamese copies), 2008 (Box 80, Folder 958)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation West Africa (4 copies, 2 editions), 2007, 2010; 2010 (Box 80, Folder 959)
  - Regional Brochure - Ford Foundation Brazil (2 copies), 2006 (Box 81, Folder 960)
  - Leadership Development in the Native Arts and Culture Sector, Miriam Jorgensen and Rachel Starks, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 961)
    Native Nations Institute for Leadership, Management and Policy, Udall Center for Studies in Public Policy, University of Arizona
  - Momentum: Sustaining Efforts to Improve Life Outcomes Among African-American Males, A Report Prepared for the Ford Foundation, Micah Gilmer, Marcus Littles, Ryan Bowers, 2008 December (Box 81, Folder 962)
  - 1951-1961: A Ten Year Report of the Fund for Adult Education (Box 81, Folder 963)
  - Native Arts and Cultures: Research, Growth and Opportunities for Philanthropic Support (2 copies), 2010 (Box 81, Folder 964)
  - 12 Who Are Changing the World: Ford Foundation Visionaries Awards (2 copies), 2012 (Box 81, Folder 965)
  - Close to Home: Case Studies of Human Rights Work in the United States (2 copies), 2004 (Box 81, Folder 966)
  - Ford Foundation International Fellowships Program Report 2003-2004: Learning, Leadership, Commitment (Box 81, Folder 967)
  - HIV/AIDS Roundtable, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, 2001 January 15-16 (Box 81, Folder 968)
    Organized by the Ford Foundation in collaboration with the Vietnam National AIDS Standing Bureau and with assistance from the Center for Educational Exchange with Vietnam
  - At the Crossroads: A Study of Federal HIV/AIDS Advocacy, Derek Hodel, 2004 May (Box 81, Folder 969)
  - Works in Progress: A Status Report on the Neighborhood and Family Initiative, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 970)
  - Sexuality & Social Change: Making the Connection, Strategies for Action and Investment (2 copies), 2007 January (Box 81, Folder 971)
  - Solving the Math Problem: The Ford Foundation's Work on Reforming Middle- and Secondary- School Mathematics, 1990-1998, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 972)
  - Pathways to Higher Education: A Ford Foundation Global Initiative for Promoting Inclusiveness in Higher Education, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 973)
  - Why We Can't Wait: A Case for Philanthropic Action: Opportunities for Improving Life Outcomes for African American Males, A Report Prepared for the Ford Foundation, Marcus L. Littles and Micah Gilmer (2 copies), 2008 January (Box 81, Folder 974)
  - The Ford Foundation India and Nepal: Statement of Current Interests 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 975)
  - The Ford Foundation in China, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 976)
  - The Ford Foundation in Indonesia: Current Interests, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 977)
  - A Foundation Returns to School: Strategies for Improving Public Education, Janice Petrovich, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 978)
  - Ford Foundation President's Review - Annual Report 1993, 1994 June (Box 82, Folder 979)
  - 1994 Ford Foundation Annual Report - President's Review (2 copies), 1995 (Box 82, Folder 980)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report 1995 - President's Review, 1996 March (Box 82, Folder 981)
  - Ford Foundation 1996 Annual Report - President's Message (2 copies), 1997 June (Box 82, Folder 982)
  - Ford Foundation 1997 Annual Report - President's Message, 1998 August (Box 82, Folder 983)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report 1998 - President's Message, 1999 June (Box 82, Folder 984)
  - Ford Foundation - President's Message 1999, 2000 May (Box 82, Folder 985)
    Reprinted from the 1999 Ford Foundation Annual Report
  - Ford Foundation - Essays from the Annual Report 2000 (2 copies), 2001 May (Box 82, Folder 986)
    Reprinted from the Ford Foundation's Annual Report and includes the President's and Vice President's essays/message
  - Ford Foundation - Essays from the Annual Report 2001 (2 copies), 2002 May (Box 82, Folder 987)
    Reprinted from the Ford Foundation's 2001 Annual Report and includes the President's and Vice President's Message/Essays
  - Program Publication - From the Ground Up: Building Assets Through Development Finance, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 988)
  - Program Publication - Asset Building for Social Change: Pathways to Large-Scale Impact, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 989)
  - Program Publication - Building Assets to Reduce Poverty and Injustice (2 copies), 2002 (Box 82, Folder 990)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (2 copies), 1992 September (Box 82, Folder 991)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1993 October (Box 82, Folder 992)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1994 September (Box 82, Folder 993)
  - Innovations in American Government 1997 - Achieving Excellence, Building Trust and Partnership for Trust in Government, 1997 November (Box 82, Folder 994)
    An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University in Partnership with the Council for Excellence in Government
  - Employment in Developing Nations, Report on a Ford Foundation Study, Edgar O. Edwards (2 copies, slightly different editions), 1974 (Box 82, Folder 995, Box 83, Folder 996)
  - Corporate Social Responsibility and the Institutional Investor, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Bevis Longstreth and H. David Rosenbloom (2 copies), 1973 (Box 83, Folder 997)
  - Roundtable Justice: Case Studies in Conflict Resolution, Reports to the Ford Foundation, Edited by Robert B. Goldman, Westview Special Studies in Peace, Conflict, and Conflict Resolution, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 998)
  - New Patterns for College Lending: A Ford Foundation Report, D. Bruce Johnstone (2 copies), 1972 (Box 83, Folder 999)
  - Different Strokes: Pathways to Maturity in the Boston Ghetto, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Robert Rosenthal, Bernard Bruce, Faith Dunne, Florence Ladd, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 1001)
  - Investing for Social Gain: Reflections on Two Decades of Program-Related Investments - PRI Book II MS File, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 1002-1006, Box 85, Folder 1007)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Drafts and Press Materials (Box 85, Folder 1008-1009)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Oversize Proofreader Copies (Box 114, Folder 1327)
  - Job 96-19B: Forestry for Sustainable Rural Development - Lists, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 1010-1011)
  - Job 98-07: Seizing Opportunities: The Role of CDCs in Urban Economic Development - Lists, Printing Correspondence, and Press Materials, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 1012, Box 86, Folder 1013)
  - Prints and Printmaking, Bruce R. Shobaken, George W. Zoretich, and Edwin W. Zoller, Center for Continuing Liberal Education of The Pennsylvania State University, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 1014)
  - Prints and Printmaking - Plates - Series A, undated (Box 86, Folder 1015)
    Prints that accompanied Prints and Printmaking - reproduced by University Prints, Boston, etchings and engravings held by museums such as the Museum of Fine Arts in Boston, the Weyhe Gallery in New York, and the National Gallery in Washington
  - Prints and Printmaking - Plates - Series B, undated (Box 86, Folder 1016)